<html>
<head>
<link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="\NINTENDO\Zelda.css">
</head>
<body>
<div class="container">

<h1 style="color:red;">18) Tokyo Mirage Sessions #FE</h1>

<b>Developer:</b> Atlus<br>
<b>Publisher:</b> Nintendo<br>
<b>Genre:</b> Role playing<br>
<b>Year Released:</b> 2016<p>

<h2>Summary:</h2>
<i>Tokyo Mirage Sessions ♯FE</i> is a role-playing video game (RPG), and a crossover between the Shin Megami Tensei and Fire Emblem series. Set in modern-day Tokyo, the game follows the members of a talent agency during their conflicts with hostile beings from another world called Mirages. To help them, the main cast are allied with friendly Mirages inspired by characters from multiple Fire Emblem games. The game's story is split up into several chapters, with the player also able to participate in side stories for various playable and supporting characters, as well as take quests from non-playable characters (NPCs) in Tokyo. The game alternates between real-world Tokyo and the Idolaspheres—alternate dimensions where enemy Mirages roam.<p>

Players control main protagonist Itsuki as he explores both worlds, interacting with various characters. Players are able to spend money earned from battles to purchase restorative items which replenish health points (HP) and energy points (EP). Players can also purchase protective accessories, with shops offering lottery tickets allowing players to win additional items. Players can also find various items in the Idolospheres, either by finding hidden treasure chests or defeating enemies in battle. The Wii U GamePad displays an in-game social app known as Topic where players can receive messages from other characters, keep updated on available Unity fusions, and view a map of each area.<p>


<center><h2>Screenshots</h2><br></center>
<center>
<img src="\TOP 30 XBOX GAMES OF ALL TIME\TOKYO MIRAGE SESSIONS S1.jpg" height=450 width=700>
<img src="\TOP 30 XBOX GAMES OF ALL TIME\TOKYO MIRAGE SESSIONS S2.jpg" height=450 width=700>
<img src="\TOP 30 XBOX GAMES OF ALL TIME\TOKYO MIRAGE SESSIONS S3.jpg" height=450 width=700>
<img src="\TOP 30 XBOX GAMES OF ALL TIME\TOKYO MIRAGE SESSIONS S4.jpg" height=450 width=700>
</center>

</div>
</body>
</html>



